

agielasyari1@gmail.com

62896-4340-8570

Q

Kenjeran, Surabaya

Agielasyari.com

ın

linkedin.com/in/agiel-asy-aria159b08a



@agielasyari11

()

github.com/agielasyari1



instagram.com/agielasyari1

SKILLS

PHP (Laravel, Codeigniter)

Javascript (ReactJs, VueJs, Gatsby)

Python

Java

LANGUAGES

Indoneisa

Professional Working Proficiency

English

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Hiking

Swimming

Travelling

Muhammad Agiel Asy'ari

Front end developer

I'm Muhammad Agiel Asy'ari. I'm currently studying at University of Trunojoyo, an Information Systems in the final semester. I am a person who has high morale, very happy to accept new challenges and experiences. I'm good at web development. I currently have 1 year front-end development experience, 1 year full development experience, 3 years team work experience

EDUCATION

Information System University of Trunojoyo

07/2017 - Present,

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front end developer Code for AsiaLtd

12/2019 - 02/2020,

Digital innovations by bringing an ecosystem of private, public and people sectortal entstogether to connect, cocreate and collaborate for the greater good. Put simply, we teach coding to complete beginners through Problem-based Learning and build cross-platform, digital products

ORGANIZATIONS

SurabayaDev (08/2018 - Present)

Core Team

Code for Asia (01/2019 - 12/2019)

Lead Chapter Bangkalan

Google Developer Groups Surabaya (02/2019)

Core Team

Developer Student Club (12/2018 - Present)

Core Team

Engineering English Community (12/2017 - 12/2019)

Head Department

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Laundry Management System (2018)

Project to help manage the web-based laundry business in managing customers, finance, etc.

Fertilizer Supply System (03/2019 - 12/2019)

Arranging inventory of fertilizers and other goods in several inventory warehouses.

Event Platform (12/2018 - 05/2019)

Assist in processing participant data event

Tobacco Inventory System (12/2019)

Managing the sale and purchase of tobacco



Singapore

My Website